Dawn mist above quiet mud houses and
empty dirt streets in a small rural
village
A barefoot boy in a faded beige
shirt stands alone outside a cracked clay
house
holding a small cloth bag
Boy walks slowly through dusty village paths
as golden morning light falls across his
face
Old
dry field with cracked earth stretches endlessly
under a pale
colorless sky
Boy kneels on hard ground
opens cloth bag
revealing a handful of simple seeds
Boy’s eyes reflect rising sun
filled with quiet determination and belief
Boy digs into dry soil with bare
hands
dust coating his skin as the earth
resists
Boy carefully places a single seed into
the ground
covering it with rough
dusty fingers
Boy lifts cracked metal pot and pours
water onto the soil
earth absorbs every drop
Dark clouds gather above the field
wind bends dry grass
air grows heavy with anticipation
Rain falls softly
then harder
Boy stands still in rain
eyes closed
face lifted
After rain
field looks transformed—soft
dark
glistening soil under cloudy sky
alive
Tiny green sprout breaks through wet soil
fragile and full of hope
Boy sits quietly beside the small sprout
at sunset
warm light surrounds them
gentle smile
Days pass
skies change
seasons shift as the sprout slowly grows
into a small plant
Plant becomes a young tree standing firm
in the field
leaves move gently in the wind
Villagers gather nearby
watch the growing tree with curiosity and
amazement
Children play and rest in the shade
of the tree
laughter fills the air
Years later
older boy stands beside tall tree at
golden sunset
looks at it with pride
Village transformed
green fields stretch across land
life returns
tall tree at center under hopeful sky